<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Companies on Career Orientation Days</title><link>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/mathematics/</link><description>Recent content in Companies on Career Orientation Days</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/mathematics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ASML</title><link>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/mathematics/asml/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 19:01:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/mathematics/asml/</guid><description>Use the most advanced mathematics to solve the physical challenges of nanometer precision. Our mathematicians break new ground by developing computational models of physical phenomena, helping to optimize ASML systems. Focus on data science and machine learning to deal with huge datasets or tackle model-based scanner control, parameter inference and more – the world of math at ASML is vast.
ASML is changing the world, one nanometer at a time! We’re a high-tech, Netherlands-based company manufacturing complex lithography systems that chipmakers use to produce integrated circuits – aka microchips.</description></item><item><title>Blue Radix</title><link>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/mathematics/blue_radix/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 19:01:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/mathematics/blue_radix/</guid><description>Ready to solve major global challenges with algorithms?
Blue Radix creates automated intelligence for daily decisions in the greenhouse. With the continuous growth of the world population, the need for healthy food is increasing. The greenhouse horticulture business is currently scaling up on a global level. But this scale up cannot be achieved due to a lack of crop experts. At the same time, energy management is increasing in complexity. We have a solution for these worldwide challenges: our algorithm-based solutions offer growers a digital brain for their greenhouse.</description></item><item><title>ORTEC</title><link>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/mathematics/ortec/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 19:01:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/mathematics/ortec/</guid><description>We are ORTEC, a purpose-driven organization changing businesses and society at large through the power of data-driven mathematical optimization. We make businesses more efficient, more predictable and more effective. Turning complex challenges into easy-to-use solutions.
ORTEC’s products result in optimized fleet routing and dispatch, vehicle and pallet loading, workforce scheduling, delivery forecasting, logistics network planning and warehouse control.
Besides our products we offer tailor-made solutions for our customers. We are experienced in areas such as: predictive maintenance and asset management, operations and supply chain analytics (i.</description></item></channel></rss>