<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Companies on Career Orientation Days</title><link>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/computer_science/</link><description>Recent content in Companies on Career Orientation Days</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 11:52:18 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/computer_science/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deloitte</title><link>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/computer_science/deloitte/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 19:01:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/computer_science/deloitte/</guid><description>You want a job with impact. At an employer where you can make a difference. Deloitte is such an employer. With over 7,000 people in 15 offices across the Netherlands, Deloitte is one of the largest providers of professional services in the areas of accountancy, tax advisory, consultancy, risk management and financial advisory. We can only do this if the best people choose us. Students with a broad view, who work in multidisciplinary teams on challenging assignments and thereby enrich their knowledge and experience.</description></item><item><title>UbiOps</title><link>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/computer_science/ubiops/</link><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 19:01:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://kaspervaessen.github.io/companies/computer_science/ubiops/</guid><description>UbiOps is a fast-growing software scale-up based in The Hague. With 20 young, creative and open- minded colleagues from 10 different countries we have a mission to let every individual and organisation activate, manage and share their data-driven intelligence.
UbiOps is a powerful yet easy-to-use platform for turning your Python and R code in live data-driven applications in minutes. UbiOps offers you a feature rich deployment and serving layer for your data science code, models and scripts.</description></item></channel></rss>